Guide to the Pete Hamill Papers BCMS.0081
Brooklyn Collection
- Series 1: Subject Files
  - Sub-series 1.1: A-Z
    - Sports Panel 16, circa 2016 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Stork Club Review, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Story Ideas, 2008-2010 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Strand, 2012-2018 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Subway Series, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - SVA, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - St. John's University, Doctor of Letters*, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - T, 2009, 2016 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Tabloids, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - TBR Review/Tinti, 2017 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Tenement Museum, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Tenement Museum 4/26, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - They Are Us, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Times Panel 2/12, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Times Panel 3/12, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Times Bk. Review-Business, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - TNR, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Toibin Review, 1999-2018 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Tokyo Sketches, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Toole, Fx, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Toots Shor, 1974, 2004-2006 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - U, 2006-2019 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Unused, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Up on the Roof, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - V, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Vietnam, 1965, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Village Voice, 2016-2017 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - W, 2007, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Westport 9/23, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Westport Tribute/03, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - WGAE, 2015-2016 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - What Mexico Taught Me, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Who's Who, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Willie Mays, 1996-2010 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Why Art Matters, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Wild Geese/Mar 4, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Writing, circa 2010 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Writing/Piece, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - WTC/Foto Intro, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - WTC/Health, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Yale, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Yiddish Books, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - NYU, 2017-2018 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - NYU/Abu Dhabi, 2017-2018 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - NYU/Conver, 2014-2018 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - NYU Events PH, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - NYU/Florence, 2017-2018 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - NYU Langone, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - NYU Mex Panel 4/19, 2015-2017 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Police Panel, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Yellow Hankie, Ribbon, 1997, 2008, 2015-2018 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sub-series 1.2: A-Z
    - 27 Words, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Academic Offers, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Aridjis, H., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Bloomberg/Hamill Intvw., 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Bloomberg 4/9, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Blurbs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - "Body and Soul" False Start, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Boxing Book Intro, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Brooklyn Book Fest, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Brooklyn Public Library, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Corbett, Steve. Interview Transcript, circa 1990 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Cosmo/Sports, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Danticat, E., 2004 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Dinnerstein Book Intro, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Donoghue, Bill, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Drinking Life Outline, circa 1993 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Dublin/Revisions, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Gelb Review, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Ginzburg, Ralph, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Harvard, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Heaney, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Heaney/1st Draft, 1989, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Heaney/Marie Transcripts, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Ireland, Heaney, 1984, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Hoagland, Ted, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Irish Face/Intro, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Orgs, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Kennedy/Gonzalez, 1994, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Gonzalez/Clips, 1992-2000 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - King, Stephen, 2002-2003, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Lars, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - LATS Columns, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Levine, David, 1989, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Liebling, A.J., 2000-2001, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Liebling Event, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Lovebooks, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Machiavelli, 1997-2010 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Miller, Tom, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Monacelli Book, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Morality/Craft, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - "News" First Draft with Gethers Notes, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - News is a Verb, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - News is a Verb/Notes, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - News Foto/Rev., circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Norfolk, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - NY Novel, circa 1990 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - O'Hanlon Intro, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Panama Novel, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - The Last Good Year, Outline*, circa 1992 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Pos. Columns, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Riggio, Steve, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Robinson, AMEX, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Ross, Lilian, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Runyon Award, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Shwartz, Ron, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Spillan, M., 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Stanky, Eddie and Baseball, 1951-1952, 1968, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Times/Sport Book, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Tinti/1st Draft, 2017 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Voice 96, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Vanity Fair/Bruce Webber, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Various Pieces, 1985-2000 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Letters, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Series 2: Speeches
  - Speeches, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Speeches/Newspapers, 1999-2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis 2012 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CT Form 6-27-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dec 10/Spch/Roughs/Tribute, 2018 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Dec. 10th Tribute, 2018 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Boston Uni, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Javits '10, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Speech Topics 2007 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Speech 2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Speeches 2006, 2000-2006 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - AIGA/Mar 22, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Bexley/4/30, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn 5/12, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn Book/Sept 16, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Budd Schulberg 2009/9/12 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Casasola/D.C. 5/15, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Credit Suisse 10/15, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Croton Speech, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - CUNY Speech, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Delaney/Folger, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Downtown Alliance 2008, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Down Block 9/23, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Dutchess Co 9/15, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Farm Credit, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Fifth Av. Committee, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Financial, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Glucksman 9/8, 1986, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Greenwood, 2011-2012 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Hamilton/Madison, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Hartford 4/10, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Harvard/ 2/26, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Hudson Co Nov 8, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - IFC, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Irish-Mex 12/8/10, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Italian-AMS 9/26, 2003, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Loretta Gluckman, circa 2010 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Kock/Jews+Irish 07, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Koch/MCNY, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Miami Nov 19-20, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Midland/Chicago, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Morgan Library 2010 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Mohegan Sun, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Morgan/5-9, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Moynihan Lecture, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - NPC, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Newark/Oct 22, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Newspapers/09/VT, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - North River, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - N.Y. Academy of Art, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - NYPL/ 10/14, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - 10/7 Ocean City NJ, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Speech May 2, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - One Book/Conn, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - 1/10/11 Palm Bch., 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Players, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - 4/56 Rockland Co., 2007 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - SIA/Oct 27, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - St. John's 4-6-05, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - St. Francis, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - St. John's May 15, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - St. John's Oct 3, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - St. Joseph's Oct 8/08, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - St. Peter's '05, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Dec 5/Shalom Ireland, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Sinn Fein June 09, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Smithsonian, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Soros/Rich 11/15, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - They Are Us Speech, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Transfig/Nov 5, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Tobin/Speech S.B., 2007 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Tucson Speech, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Town, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Dec 4/"Y" with Greenfield, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - 7/18 Yale, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Watertown, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Wild Geese, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - WTC Foto Shon, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Speeches, 2011-2012 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Speeches, 2009-2012 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Tenn.09, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Prospect Park 10-5-2019 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Immigration, circa 2010 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Speech Notes*, circa 2000-2010 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- Series 3: Writing
  - Sub-series 3.1: Scripts and Treatments
    - Kid-First Draft*, circa 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Kid-Second Draft*, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Kid*, circa 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The Quarter/The Tenement/Across the Border/Baja Beat*, circa 1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Gaslight City-Final Draft*, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Gaslight*, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - City of Islands*, circa 2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Mexico*, circa 1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - City of Islands/Prelude to a Kiss*, 1998-circa 2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Why Leonardo Matters*, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Villa!-4th Draft*, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - The Yellow Flag*, circa 2009 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Border, circa 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Briscoe Outlines, circa 1995 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Briscoe TV/2, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Brooklyn Reader, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Christmas Play, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Gallo, Bill, 1992, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Girl Singer, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - New Orleans/New Awlin, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - NOLA, circa 1985 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - New York/TV Series, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Newsbite, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - On the Border, circa 1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Outline for Bill Powers, circa 1988 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Pete Hamill on Eddie Stanky, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - The Play, circa 1988 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Pros and Cons Script, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - The Quarter, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Red, White and Blue, circa 1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Schulberg, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Shabbos Goy, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Soldiers Pension, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Soldiers Pension, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Spaldeen Summer, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Split Images, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 38-39)
    - Why Art Matters, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Sub-series 3.2: Books and Articles
    - City, circa 1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Snow in August: Notes, Plans, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Snow in August: Goy-First Draft, circa 1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Snow in August: Goy- Revisions, Edits, ect., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Snow in August: Menachem (notes), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Snow in August: The Magic Words*, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
    - Snow in August: Manuscript*, circa 1996 (Box 10, Folder 22-24)
    - Snow in August: Corrected Pages*, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
    - Snow in August: Proofs *, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Snow in August: Proofs*, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
    - Snow in August: Original Manuscript, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Snow in August: Westport Reads, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Snow in August", 1978, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - "The Prague Ghetto" by Milada Vilímková, 1993 (Box 11, Object 1)
    - Snow in August: Fan Mail, 1977-2011 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Snow in August: General, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Snow in August: Reviews, 1997-1998, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Snow in August: Queries, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Snow in August: Paperback, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Snow in August: Movie Ink, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Snow in August: Japan, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Snow in August, 1955, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Snow in August: Foreign, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Snow in August: Europe, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Snow in August: Clinton, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Snow in August: Answered, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Snow in August: ALA, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Snow in August: Showtime, 1999-2002 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Snow in August: PS146, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - "Forever", 2003, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Forever: Biz, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Forever: Edits, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Forever: Ireland, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Forever: Knockoff, 2006-2008 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Forever: Knockoff, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Forever: Knockoff, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Forever: Knockoff-Fans, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Forever: Knockoff-Lawsuit, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Forever: Knockoff, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Forever: Lists, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Forever: Mistakes, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Forever: Paperwork, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Forever: Phillips, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Forever: Press Kit, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Forever: Promotion, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Forever: Radical Media Project, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Forever: Fans, 2002-2006 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Forever: Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Forever: Sked, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Forever: Terry, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Forever: Handwritten, circa 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Forever: Novel Pages, circa 2000 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Downtown: Full Phillips Notes, circa 2004 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Downtown: Revisions 1-80, circa 2004 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Downtown: Outline, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Downtown: Audio, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 32-33)
    - Downtown: Promotion, 2004-2006 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Downtown: Reviews, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Downtown: Times Review, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Downtown: Fifth Ave., 2003 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - *Downtown: Notes, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Downtown: Orange Riots, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Downtown: Trinity, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Downtown: General, 2004, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Downtown: Phillips, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Downtown: PB/CX, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Downtown: Japan, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Downtown: Mistakes, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Downtown: Hamill Notes, circa 2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Downtown: Flaps/Biz, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Downtown: Fans, Friends, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Downtown: Cover, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Downtown: Cover/2nd, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Downtown: Collection, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Downtown: Copy Edits, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Downtown: Audio, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Downtown: Ireland House, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Downtown: Edits, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Downtown: Zainab, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Downtown: SKED, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Downtown: Page Proofs, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 40-41)
    - North River: Asya, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - North River: Asya's Notes, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - North River: Copy Edits ect., 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - North River: Cover, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - North River/Downtown: Fales, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - North River: Flaps/Early Reacts, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - North River: Foreign, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - North River: Movies, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - North River: Paperback, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - North River: Permissions, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - North River: Promotion, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - North River: Reviews, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - North River: Times Review, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - North River: Tour/Events, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - North River: O'Reilly Mail, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - North River: Master, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
    - North River: Spine Copy, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
    - North River: Proofs, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
    - North River: General, 2007-2013 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - North River: Catalog, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - North River: Corr. 05-06, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - North River: Fans, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - North River: Permissions, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - North River: Publicity, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - North River: Reviews, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - North River: Rights, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - North River: 1934 Timeline, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - North River: Giants, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - North River: Radios/Songs, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Vietnam: General, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Vietnam: AP Memos, ect., 2011-2012 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Vietnam: Intro, 2013-2015 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Vietnam: Finished 9/4/2012 1:52 PM (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Vietnam: Edits, 1945, 1950, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Vietnam: AP Photo Book, 2011-2012 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Vietnam: General, 1999-2011 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Vietnam: 2, 2012-2013 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Vietnam: Research/Oral Histories*, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Vietnam: Saigon Bureau, 1963-1975, 2005-2011 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Vietnam: Saigon Reporters, 1995-2012 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Vietnam: Adams, Eddie, 2004-2009 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Vietnam: Arnett, Peter, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Vietnam: Browne, Malcolm, 1998, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Vietnam: Capa, Robert, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Vietnam: Fall, Bernard, circa 2012 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Vietnam: Horst Faas, 2007-2012 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Vietnam: Richard Pyle, 2005-2012 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Vietnam: Ut, Nick, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Vietnam: Nick Ut/Hal Buell, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Vietnam: My Lai/Kent State, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Vietnam: Glossary- Press Casualties, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Vietnam: Samples, 1951-1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Belfast Novel: General, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Belfast Novel: 1907 Strike (Larkin), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Belfast Novel: Belfast 1870-1921, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Belfast Novel: Belfast 1910-20. Titanic, Halley's Comet, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Belfast Novel: Misc-1910-20, circa 2008 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Belfast Novel: Belfast 2008 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Belfast Novel: Belfast Celtic, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Belfast Novel: Falls Road, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Belfast Novel: Falls Road, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Belfast Novel: West, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Belfast Novel: In Belfast Town, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Belfast Novel: Billy Dillon Notes/George, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Belfast NovelL Belfast Guide*, circa 2005, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Belfast Novel: Billy Dillon pp. 1-22 Notes, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Belfast Novel: Carnduff, T., 1991-1994, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Belfast Novel: Cinemas, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Belfast Novel: Education 1902-'50, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Belfast Novel: Edwardian Belfast, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Belfast Novel: Halley's Comet, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Belfast Novel: Irish Timeline, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Belfast Novel: Music Halls, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Belfast Novel: Schools, circa 2000 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Belfast Novel: Churches/Schools, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Belfast Novel: Soccer, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Belfast Novel: New York Soccer 1920s, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Belfast Novel: Songs, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Belfast Novel: TBR/Carr Book, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Belfast Novel: "Images of East Belfast," Notes*, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Belfast Novel: "Belfast in the 1940's," Atlas*, 2005-2008 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Belfast Novel: "Forgotten Shipbuilders of Belfast"*, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Belfast Novel: Research, Notes*, circa 2008 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Belfast Novel: Research, Notes*, 1976-1977, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Belfast Novel: Research, Notes*, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Belfast Novel: Soccer Magazines*, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Belfast Novel: Research*, 1916, 1991-2013 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Belfast Novel: Research, Notes*, 1916-2008 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Belfast Novel: Research, Notes, 1971, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Belfast Novel: Research, Notes, Correspondence*, circa 1970-2008 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Belfast Novel: Research, Notes*, 1916, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Note From Fukiko Aoki-Hamill*, circa 2019 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bob Best: Memos, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bob Best: Research, Correspondence*, 1914-2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Bob Best: I, 1943-1952 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bob Best: 2, 1943-1948 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Bob Best: Roughs, circa 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Bob Best: Austria, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Bob Best: Nazis, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Drinking, 1965-1964, 1985-1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Drinking Life, 1994-2015 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Tabloid City: Characters, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Tabloid City: Notes on Final/Title, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Tabloid City: Malik, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Tabloid City: Notes, circa 2009 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Tabloid City: Used Roughs, circa 2009 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Tabloid City: Phillips, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Tabloid City: Bill/Asya/Final, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Tabloid City: Phillips/Edits Jan 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Tabloid City: June 9 to BP, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Tabloid City: Edits, circa 2010 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Tabloid City: Page Printout, circa 2010 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Tabloid City: Manuscript, circa 2010 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Downtown: Manuscript, circa 2005 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Tabloid City: Manuscript (FH), circa 2010 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Tabloid City: Characters, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Tabloid City: Manuscript, Notes*, circa 2010 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Tabloid City: Marketing*, 2010-2015 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Tabloid City: City Outlines, ect., 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Tabloid City: City Outline, circa 1990 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Christmas Kid: Correspondence, Promotion*, 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Christmas Kid: Asya, CK Paper, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Christmas Kid: Copy Edits, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Christmas Kid: Misc., 2011-2012 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Christmas Kid: Reviews, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Christmas Kid: Promotion, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Christmas Kid: Tales of New York Short Stories*, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Christmas Kid: Short Stories, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Christmas Kid: Manuscript, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Astor, Brooke, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Misc., 2005-2008 (Box 14, Folder 36)